sync.gioni666
Show yourself!
I know you're there!
Help! Helping me!
Helping me!
WOLF MAN ~ ~
Translation and adaptation: Felixuca
Nifty Subtitles Team (c) www.niftyteam.ro
Talbot  Dear sir,
think your brother has mentioned to me
in his correspondence.
My name is Gwen Conliffe,
Ben's fiancee.
I am writing to inform you
about your brother's disappearance
is missing a few weeks
and our fears are black.
I understand that you are currently
here in England,
your theater company,
but would you come back soon
in America.
understand that you have not talked to relatives
for many years ...
... but I beg you helping us
Ben to find it.
Please, come home,
at Talbot Hall.
Anybody?
Samson!
Lawrence?
Hi, Dad.
See the  it, reads:
Wandering son returned.
I hope not you'd expect
viþelul to cut the fat.
And eZi!
Not very first visit.
You seem to go well.
Often I wondered
May look like.
I suppose you came because
your brother. And eZi.
Yes.
Ms. Conliffe found that are in London.
- Samson!
- And I sent a letter ...
... telling me that Ben has gone.
Father, we offer you my help ...
What great idea.
Lawrence is a great idea.
Unfortunately your brother's body
was found in a ditch,
next road to the monastery,
yesterday morning.
I suppose that's something dressed
the funeral.
Sir John!
Remember you are my son
Lawrence?
Singh, my servant.
Master Lawrence.
Good to see you,
Lawrence.
It's good you're here.
Ms. Conliffe was announced?
It's up in the bedroom dance
asleep.
Þin where Ben's body?
Father yours told me to bury
things your brother with him.
I was thought it sin.
Thank you.
I Do not do it, sir.
It ...
I never saw almost
his entire life.
I do not think it was a beast.
It was a cunning murderers.
Someone who shall bear a grudge
one of these people.
To induce authorities in error,
I and Kill shower Manuli,
SFA then it displayed the body as to seem
that made it a wild animal.
Ridiculous!
And who would give so much trouble?
That dance of the Gypsies Security Bear
could have to do.
Blestemãþia! But I doubt
you can kill three people.
I saw corpses
with my own eyes.
They were hurt are unnatural,
are very unnatural.
I say that he did
fierce creature.
You damn Gypsies who wandered
drãcoveniile bringing this to them!
Q and are appearance and over
two weeks to spend it!
I say that Ben Talbot
went to their camp
that you-and make the head
þigancã a slut.
The bear put his paw on
and threw what was left of it in the ditch!
Had no connection with þiganii.
After 25 years,
Dad found him.
NODDY Quinn and all his flock,
dogs and goats and May God knows what,
lepãdaþi throughout MLA and Tina,
on a quarter of mile.
Quinn's is not grateful and tea face.
Like he was eaten alive.
Creature who had done
was great ...
have claws
and less and that could not killing.
After that,
Dad went home
and melt cutlery wedding
mother.
He did gloanþe Silver
of them.
It no longer exit the house
the full moon was from then on.
I still say that the bear's fault.
We can help, sir?
I hope I can talk
with Miss Conliffe.
One moment, sir.
Miss Conliffe ...
- I am Lawrence.
- I know who you are.
Sorry to meet such.
They have belonged to Ben.
And I would like to receive them are you.
If you need anything,
all,
please tell me.
I want to know what happened.
- I will do everything I will stand putinþã.
- Thank you.
Thank you for coming.
Today I saw Ben's body.
What kind of animal
could have done so what?
I saw what may be a Panther
or a Bengal tiger,
most ferocious beasts of nature
but you gotta admit
that I have never seen so something.
People tell city
that a bear did it.
A and say that rather
a dangerous lunatic.
If it were possible,
I think I would wild dogs.
On the other hand,
crime is so awful that the ...
Only a man would be able
also intentional malice.
Among the things Ben
I found a strange medallion.
St. Columbanus,
was a saint in the East.
And I was Gypsies.
So Ben had job
with þiganii?
She was ... Our negotiator.
Humanity of the place
pay a fee
and commit as few þiganii
misdeeds as possible ...
and will leave again after
will be sold to young men around here ...
as wine and "ladies tuciurii" may lead.
Virgo  heavenly fire burdened white
that mortals tell Month
slide, sparkling,
the wool of my back ...
printer and midnight tiatã of-breath.
(Percy Bysshe Shelley, "cloud")
Exert immense power,
not you?
I would like things
to be otherwise.
It never looked behind, Lawrence.
It never looked behind.
Past
is a wild kingdom of horrors.
Lawrence?
I'm glad you're home.
Mother!
Lawrence  ...
Lawrence.
Lawrence, wake you up.
I heard something.
Lawrence  ...
Lawrence, I'm afraid.
Go back to bed.
Mother?
Mother !...
- Hi.
Ben said that here you play
when you were young.
It was our refuge.
Compared to what?
You mean "compared to whom".
Your father ...
has a Fire Dist.
Ben told me it's because
remind you of your mother.
I told you and you do it.
Therefore I closed in a hospice
a full year.
Then I sent in my rectum and
America.
Sure do not want to stay
evening?
My dad found a hostel.
It's easier
trains.
- When you return to London?
- When you find out what my brother pãþit.
All good and beautiful, but I
you better have to wait until tomorrow.
Tonight's full moon and I. ..
to and prefer to stay in the house,
the idea that your theory, the "lunaticului"
will prove correct.
I am not going
You lose and you.
Can I take your horse
cona and rad?
Good evening.
Say you have to stay in camp,
forest is dangerous.
Ask him if he knows someone
so selling something.
- Want to talk to your Malev.
- Who?
Malev.
It was found on
My brother's body.
There was your caravan ...
three people were killed and I.
I do not think that is a coincidence.
It is no coincidence.
It's fate hand,
but she played with books on the table.
And you my story about my brother.
Come!
Give us the bear, dresorule!
- We know what happens.
- Dance. Just dancing.
Come on!
What's happening?
I came across a large animal.
We killed people.
- For God.
- It's harmless.
- What happened?
- Is the devil! Devil!
Mother! Mother!
Maria! Where are you, Mary?
Maria!
Maria ...
- There!
- Maria!
Maria!
Mother!
Stay in the tent!
Boys ...
Boy!
Bring help!
Once that is how muscle beast
there is no cure.
We should leave him to die.
That would be a sinful.
There is no sin
if you kill a beast.
Is not it?
If you kill a man ...
are not well received
the hereafter.
Many suffered
that.
Sometimes, human fate is cruel.
May be issued
just someone who loves him.
Lady!
Help me it car, Singh.
A week ago I would say
not that you will never use your arm.
And now?
Seems to have healed.
I will come to consult you
at the end of the week.
Thank you, Doctor.
- Miss Conliffe?
- Yes.
- I want to thank.
- What?
Because you have extended
Blackmoor sitting in with us,
during this difficult period.
For you did it from a sense of ...
obedience branch
would be no trouble for me.
Lawrence tried to find out
what happened to Ben.
Now we know ...
beast is still at large.
- However, thank.
- Do not you what.
You should sleep, Lawrence.
And you.
I serve you?
You'd expect to burst
any war?
Singh is a warrior of God,
need to always equip
against evil.
Do you believe in curses?
This house was part
enough suffering.
Your mother, your brother ...
Yes, I believe in curses.
But he stayed here so many years ...
It was bound to do.
Silver.
- I knew not hunt mon ones.
- Sometimes you mon masters and hunt you.
It was pretty badly injured, Inspector.
Suffer from memory loss,
I do not think it will be of any help.
I think at some point
will want to talk about ...
I see. And if I could
to exchange a few words ...
- ... Completely unofficial ...
- No, no.
Up and the shortest meeting
sure I would be very helpful.
Francis Adderly,
Scotland Yard.
It's an honor to meet you, Mr Talbot.
I am a great admirer.
I'm sorry to hear
troubles suffered
I hope you will not prevent
return to the scene.
Thank you.
- Let go?
- Please.
We understand that your wound
was quite ... wild.
Yes.
I hope you not to seem inquisitive,
but I could arrange
consider you a specialist?
It's amazing what we derive from
means scientific, today.
- When you want your course.
- Sure.
It's a mystery in view that the
England no natural predators there
able to produce
hurt so terrible.
Ferocity of the attack would suggest
action of an animal,
or ... lunatic.
Someone with serious problems
mental health,
who spent some time
in a hospice ...
who may have suffered hurt
produced by hand of his victims.
Understand what insinuaþi
and bothers me.
It is clear
that I know the past,
so how and I think
I know that the your
If somehow you have investigated
"Ripper" several years ago?
Are you a man directly,
So I have and I live with you
You are not the enemy, Mr Talbot.
But seeing you play so many roles
the same chip,
be prudent to ask who does
May "vieþuie and you" in your head
Good day, Inspector.
So you do not mind if I
say where you were last night.
How you want.
Welcome, Mr Talbot.
I will send you Specialists
consult when you want your.
Lawrence?
You're okay?
What he told the inspector?
He asked many questions.
I'm sorry. I feel so
responsible for what you pãþit ...
I would of never sent that letter
you have returned to New York.
No. Inhere to go back.
You should not feel the and a.
No.
Tries.
I can not make a jump,
like you.
We have to throw it off.
- Are you ready?
- Yes.
Never mind.
A îndrepþi up ...
Tries.
How is New York?
- Hear that?
- What?
Horses.
Hello, Doctor.
Park established consultation for Friday.
Come with us!
Approaching full-moon night.
You were muscle how beast.
Now wearing his sign.
This could be the solution.
Many of us were interested
the explanation of "natural".
Help us.
Come on, Talbot,
show us your wounds.
They say that they heal
are unnatural ways.
It can not let you kill
wives and children.
- Fuck, Talbot!
- I'm sorry, Colonel.
I wanted to shoot you.
Unfortunately, no longer a target and
as good as the old days.
- Probably older.
- It's cursed.
God was denied him.
Let us solve.
You enter and take my mo
and I could shoot you and that place right now.
My servant, Singh is on the roof
and happens to be a target and
great gun fire repeatedly.
And you will kill.
It will kill at least ten of you
By the reload and move less.
So please delete one
of my property.
And if you never see on any
entering without permission here
I will not be so civilized.
If pricepeþi what I mean.
Good day and to you, Colonel.
Lawrence ...
Bleeding.
How do you think of
it's a threat to them?
Is a stranger here in Blackmoor,
Miss Conliffe,
and therefore it is very dangerous.
Thank you.
Yes, they can thank
Singh and his ...
when he returns from the village.
There are single family
equipped to acting.
Samson!
To bring something to your wash.
You hit the shoulder?
No.
On the contrary, is stronger
than before.
That's good.
I could and þin
on all three remote.
You know you should not hear them.
Villagers are înapoiaþi and pro are.
All you hate the most
in place.
Lawrence ...
Excuse me.
- What happened?
- I gotta go.
Please do your luggage.
I did something?
There are safe here.
You have to go to London
this evening.
I expect out.
Lawrence!
Wait.
What do you fear?
If you pãþi something
I did not and never forget it.
Some doubt
the power of Satan.
Satan's power to transform
men in irons.
But no doubt the ancient pagans.
No prophets.
Daniel warned him not to Nebuchadnezzar?
But orgoliosul King
did not listened to Daniel,
and as the Bible tells us that he was
converted into a wolf and exiled people.
The Beast has come between us.
But Lord
and i will defend believers.
With his right hand,
will crush the demon apples and av.
I say, the enemy plan
is one and iret.
Turning them on the blestemaþi
in irons
wants to throw us into hell,
to transform us into animals.
Try to convince us,
that we forget that fãcuþi
the image of the Almighty himself i.
Samson.
Why tolerate our Lord
this mockery?
Pride only open path of destruction.
Spirit semeþ before fall ...
I say that is happening
because we have sinned in front of His
because of our iniquities
were echoed in Heaven
and demand revenge.
A bitter, please.
- Madam Kirk?
- Why are not out, with McQuinn ...
... until you catch that creature
who killed my husband?
Since I do not know
they will attack lunaticul,
seems almost to stand as
close to potential victims.
And seeing that some 214 of
the most important 300
inhabitants of Blackmoor
living within a radius of 500 meters
of this Tavern,
I'm going to spend the evening here.
Not at Talbot Hall?
Why did you say that?
I blestemaþi. All of us.
Unfortunately, being
"blestemaþi" I do not give permission
mo to walk at night and take Sir John.
Rules, Mrs Kirk ...
are designed to protect us
a world in which we SFA and IEM between us.
A bitter, please.
It is a shrine dedicated
your beloved mother.
A truly beautiful woman.
I know her loss
Did he hurt deeply.
It is monstrous that a Baietel
you-and seeing my mother that way.
And I would sacrifice my life
let us find you are that night.
You gotta believe me, Lawrence.
I think, do you?
I loved your mother with a passion
that burned like the sun.
Her death broke me,
I was devastated.
I still walk the night the house ...
looking for her.
But the dead remain.
Look me in the eye, Lawrence.
You see that are ...
devoid of life.
I would like to say that your tragedy
which has overshadowed your life ended.
But I'm afraid ...
that you wait
gloomy watch Hell.
I do not think you will kill Lawrence.
But you will învinovãþi.
Beast will dezlãnþui.
Beast will exit the surface.
I got it, folks!
I got him!
Find a hole, Johnny!
Johnny!
McQuinn!
Lawrence!
Wake you up.
Lawrence ...
You did some terrible things,
Lawrence.
You did some terrible things.
Do not pull!
On your knees!
It's so like you said, inspector.
It's like you said.
I'm sorry, Sir John.
Be strong, Lawrence.
Be strong.
Madhouse Lambeth, London
Where is my father?
I'm sorry to see you again
here, Lawrence.
Disappoint me are.
But I did great steps in treatment
illusions and the suffering you.
Where is dad?
Refreshing,
not so, buddy?
Where's Dad?
Where's Dad? ...
If you do not kill my father,
He comes to kill you.
Horatio, tell me one thing.
You really  Alexander
look the same in the earth?
And everything smelled so?
(Shakespeare, "Hamlet", tr. Ion Vinea)
I hope that it will not prevent
you turn on the stage.
Alas, poor Yorick!
Lawrence, wake you up.
I heard something.
Terrible things, Lawrence ...
Terrible things.
Father!
Look me in the eye, Lawrence.
You see
you are dead.
Nothing, Lawrence.
All is well.
I will go home.
Come with me.
Never mind. Come.
Never mind.
Keep me in his arms.
Just keep me in his arms.
Not real.
Licantropie. Licantropie ...
I got the disease, if it is,
in India, the Hindu Kuh.
Locals took me in on a cave
the mountains,
where, according to legend, lived
a strange creature ... very strange.
And after several days of cãþãrãri ...
and searches ...
Finally I came across it.
I found it.
I found the cave ...
and the strange creature
who live there.
It was a Baietel ...
a baby wild,
unnaturally loud.
Suddenly, I attacked.
He muscle cat.
So I returned
to my comrades hunting them
location in the valley at the foot of the mountain
believing that I had been the subject of jokes.
But soon I discovered
and that was not the a.
You killed my mother.
Yes, Lawrence,
I did.
It should
put an end to your life.
No you can not say
whenever I thought about it,
but life is too splendid, Lawrence,
especially for those blestemaþi
and condemned, like me.
The full moon nights, years in the string,
I was locked in that vault
of my faithful servant,
Singh. 25.
Then came her
hot and moon face.
Gwen.
... Occurred as illusions
of an appalling nature.
Mr. Talbot.
This evening we are here
to demonstrate decisively
fears that Mr Talbot is iraþionale.
A So ...
we remain in this room together
and the patient will find that months
full has no influence on him
that it is an absolutely ordinary man,
will be the first small step towards the long
to însãnãto and mental improvement.
And we all know that Mr Talbot
suffered
Personal experiences
trauma.
He witnessed the self-harm
his mother,
and minds of young,
unable to accept reality,
created a "really" fantastic.
That his father is to blame.
That his father is, literally,
a monster.
But ...
Your father is a werewolf.
You were muscle as a werewolf.
You will become a werewolf ...
I do not like a dog will grow wings
and I will not fly on that window.
I think Mr Talbot
has something to tell us.
Încetaþi ... Încetaþi ...
Here, Mr Talbot?
Forgive me, but you can hear.
Idiot!
Tonight
I will kill you all!
I'll kill everyone!
As you see,
I can not ...
Please, do something!
... of mind, with somewhere
in the depths ...
For him, everything seems very real.
Doctor Hoenneger!
Doctor!
Open the door to that!
It seems to be locked, sir.
- Gibbons!
- Yes, sir.
- You're armed?
Give me a revolver. Quick!
Move! Move!
I'm sorry.
- Carter!
- Sir?
- You gun?
- Yes, sir.
Follow me.
Send a telegram to Scotland Yard.
To bring guns!
- Now!
- I'm going, sir!
- Suppose that we gloanþe silver.
- What?
You two, come with me!
Doors URELIT ...
God help us!
Who's there?
Lawrence!
What Looking here?
What you have done?
They are what they say.
I am a monster.
Like my father.
He killed Ben.
And mother.
I can help.
Can not be helped.
If such things exist ...
are possible if ...
where everything is ...
Magic ...
And God ...
Can find a way to put an end.
You have to confess ...
I envy you brother
for days spent with you.
For joy to be
to be a felt.
I would give anything I ...
you have known
in another life.
I got to go to Talbot Hall
and to eliminate them.
Lawrence ...
Please let me help you.
You already did.
Lawrence, stay here with me.
Stay here with me!
Miss Conliffe,
Good morning.
Inspector.
You can bother?
Have to ask directly.
You have seen on Lawrence Talbot?
Certainly you have heard
about his escape.
Yes, I heard
and no, I've seen.
Miss Conliffe ...
I can not tell how dangerous
you have there ...
If you have found in his presence.
Thank you. You take care.
Miss Conliffe ...
I admire your noble intentions.
Believe that you can save,
but not the and a.
Have to insist
însoþiþi to me.
- Let insistaþi? Not ...
- Carter!
Not here, Inspector!
Take your hands off me!
Talbot?
Raise your hands and exit the view!
Talbot!
No!
Great luck on your head
LICANTROPIA
THE ancient teachings Gypsies
M looking for a woman named Malev.
O you know?
not here.
What you want from me?
Lawrence Talbot ...
You know what happened.
Understand. Listen to me.
Should help me.
Leave it in the arms of his fate.
Need to save.
I love you?
Just tell me what to do!
I will condemn?
Or you will release?
You know what that means?
Yes.
But I can.
No one can do. He is still there.
I know it.
I know you can save.
I beg you, tell me what to do.
There is no cure.
Do you put lives in danger.
Saints to protect you and to your
give strength to do the right thing.
- You're sure to come?
- Yeah, sure.
Well.
Go on the road to the monastery.
You go to the station.
You you go south, by river.
Show him to Sir John that we are here
and stay near mo displayed,
but not too close.
If you see the Talbot,
not sit at the discussion.
Shot move it ... and ucideþi it.
There!
Carter asked us to give you the report.
He was seen entering the house.
Miss Conliffe?
Wait!
Call them on others.
I will raise, I'll go
to my Father and I tell him ...
Father, I have sinned in front of the Sky
and in front of you
And not worthy
names are to me "your son".
See the  it, reads:
Wandering son returned.
To bring mantle
You're one of the ez and shoulders?
Let your fingers make rings
and încãlþãri up?
You should pray, although both
we know it will not help.
"Finished comedy.
(The show ended)
Those are silver gloanþele
Singh's in my gun?
I'm sorry.
Where is the downside.
- Good.
- What?
To see you here,
in this way.
My son has returned.
- It's splendid, do you?
- No, it's hell.
Hell?
Beast Beast ...
Let it run free.
Poor Lawrence ...
What are fragile.
I removed the little dust cup
the cartridges many years ago.
I confess, I was really overcome and it
of your enormous courage.
Finally you became man
that I always wanted to be.
Lawrence!
My boy.
Get up.
You see, Lawrence?
I feel the presence, power?
He will come soon,
exit from darkness to light fixtures.
You're tenitorul mo and my kingdom,
Lawrence.
Always have been modernizing and tenitorul
my kingdom.
Lawrence ... Lawrence!
No!
- Security has taken in there, sir?
- Go now.
Look me, Lawrence!
I know from You!
You know who I am.
Lawrence!
You know who I am!
Not ...
Lawrence, I know are! I know from You!
Remember you're mine. Look me.
I'm Gwen.
Lawrence, is Gwen.
Please.
Gwen.
Sorry ...
Supposed to be a and a.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
It is said that are not sin
when we take a wild animal life.
Just when you kill a man.
But where one begins
and to end it and get another?
sync.gioni666
Subtitles Felixuca
Nifty Subtitles Team (c) www.niftyteam.ro
www.moviesubtitles.org